ILGWU Pacific Northwest District Council Records 5780/207
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Vacation Fund Assets and Liabilities, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Welfare Fund: U.S. Treasury Bonds, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Vacation Fund: Farmers Home Administration (Congley R. Cox), 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Vacation Fund: U.S. Treasury Bonds, 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Welfare Fund Asset Statement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Welfare Fund Asset Statement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Welfare Fund Chronological Cash Statement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Welfare Fund Assets and Liabilities, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- General Advisory Council, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- General Advisory Council meeting, October 26, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- General Advisory Council, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- General Advisory Council, October, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- General Advisory Council, September 23, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- General Advisory Council, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- GEB, January, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- GEB, January, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- GEB, June, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- GEB, September, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- GEB, October 15-19, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- GEB, October 15-19, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- GEB, February, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- GEB, September 22, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- GEB, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- GEB reception, October 6, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Justice, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Wong, Ted, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- San Francisco Senators, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Handgun Control, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Western States region seminar, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Mattie Jackson correspondence, November-December, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Mattie Jackson correspondence, October, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Mattie Jackson correspondence, July-August, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Mattie Jackson correspondence, March-May, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Mattie Jackson correspondence, January-February, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Mattie Jackson correspondence, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Chinese American Federation of Union Members, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Communications from business agents, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Wayne's Garment Shop, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- SF Board of Supervisors, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Freitas, Joe, SF District Attorney, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Resolutions, Southern CA District Council, PNWDC, Arizona-Utah District Council, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- SF Redevelopment Agency, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Planning Committee (Don Watson), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Irwin Memorial Blood Bank, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Counseling Material for senior citizens-legal assistance, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- SF City Codes-Board of Supervisors, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- California Student Aid Commission, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Shop Stewards reports (resolution of complaints), 1981 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Resolution, SF Jt. Board, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- PNWDC Special Meeting minutes, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Margaret S. Williams, A. Phillip Randolph Institute, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Delancey St. Foundation, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Union Podiatry Group, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- SF Fair, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Welfare Fund: U.S. Treasury Bills, registered, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- PNWDC Executive Council minutes, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- NWDC minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Christmas Party; NWDC meeting and dinner, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Letters to women's groups, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Finance and Steering Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- PNWDC meeting and dinner, June 6, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- GEB "Conditions in the Women's Garment Industry", 1982 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Campaign Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Campaign contributions, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- GEB meetings, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Local 101-Oakland section, voting tally, February 17, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Myrtle Banks correspondence, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Myrtle Banks correspondence, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Coop file, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Napa-various monthly bills, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Subpoena (May Ling Tom), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Misc. publications, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Newsletters, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- NY Sweatshops, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Sweatshop articles, LA Herald Examiner, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Misc. clippings, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- loose correspondence, 1973-1984 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Pacific Coast Federation, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Western States Region Seminar, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Western States Region Seminar, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- COHOP Firm file, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Staff Retirement: Louis Rolnick, 1976-1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Staff Retirement: Louis Rolnick, 1976-1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Subpoena (Anna Strava), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Subpoena (Francisco Sanchez), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Subpoena (Luba Samosvatoff), 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Staff Retirement: Payments to NY, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- San Francisco Organizing Project, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Roofing repairs, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Histadrut bills, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- EEOC Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Complaints received (from workers), 1976-1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- California Legislature, Assembly Committee on Labor and Unemployment, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- District Attorney Family Support Division, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Administrative income, all sources, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Cuffs and Collars, Inc., 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Aaron James, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Acme Sewing Company, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- University of California, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Joseph G. Kennedy Foundation, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Mahogany Designer House and Manufacturing Corporation, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Hill, Norman, A. Philip Randolph Education Fund, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Western States Regional Staff Conference, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Industrial Relations, California Department of, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Agreements, 1947-1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Agreements, 1947-1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Home Work, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Lantos/Child Labor hearings, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Parental leave, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- CA Industrial Welfare Commission, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- CA Industrial Welfare Commission, 1988-1993 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Fair Trade Commission, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Waxman-Gephardt resolution, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- US-Mexico free trade, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- US-Mexico free trade, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Agreement, Mademoiselle Knitwear, Local 155 (NY), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Agreement, Tejidos de Coamo, Local 601 (PR), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Agreement, SF Knitworks, PNDC, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Win Fashion, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Asian American Federation of Union Members, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Asian Immigrant Women Advocates, Jessica McClintock, 1987-1998 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Asian Immigrant Women Advocates, Jessica McClintock, 1987-1998 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Asian Immigrant Women Advocates, Jessica McClintock, clippings, 1990-1998 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Asian Pacific Environmental Network, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Apparel Coalition, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Asian Law Caucus, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Coalition for Immigrant and Refugee Rights and Services, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Crossroads, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Levi-Strauss, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- LEAP (Leadership Education for Asian Pacific's), Asian American Public Policy Institute, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Northern California Chinese Garment Contractors Association, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Membership (certificates), 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Labor Law notes, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Shop stewards, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Shop stewards, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Piece rates, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Meeting dates, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Local 101, excused from meeting letters, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- All locals meeting schedules, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- NLRB- Jorge Campos, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Napa shop issues, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- ILGWU correspondence, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- T&W Fashions, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO convention, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Lilli Anu, misc., 1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Boero shop issues, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Ink works (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  n.d.
- Bay Bias Binding and Quilting Co. negotiations, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Bay Bias shop issues, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Bay Bias contracts, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Bay Bias contract negotiations, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Martna Austin, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Bay Bias non-union competition, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Bay Bias vacation, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Bay Bias vacation checks, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Bay Bias negotiations, organizing materials, information requests, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Alde issues, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Alde audit, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Alde second shift, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Alde time clock, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Gum Har Hom, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Advance Pleating Arbitration, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Memoranda of understanding extending contractors agreement, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Contractors contract, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Florence Menses, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- KL Young shop issues, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Contractors, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Misc. shop agreements, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- contract negotiations, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- contractors contract, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- GARMENT, 2000-1994 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- GARMENT; Hiring, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- GARMENT, 2000-1995 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- GARMENT, 2000-1995 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Tutson, Delores, Union label reports, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Tutson, Delores, Union label reports, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Tutson, Delores, Union label reports, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Gunne, Sax, 1985-1992 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Garment industry provision, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Garment shops, Oakland, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Golden Gate Bias, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Organizing "Using Health and Safety in Organizing", 1984 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- NUFIS (Non-Union Firms Information System) reports, 1980-1993 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- SF Shop list, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- SF Chinatown shops, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- contracting shops/manufacturers in SF and vicinity, 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- sewing services, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Winterland, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Sacramento sweatshops, 1985-1993 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Portland, Oregon shops, 1986-1994 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Seattle, WA shops, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Organizing, Washington and Oregon garment industry, 1987-1997 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Saipan, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- potential colonizers, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- organizers (resumes), 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Concuita Leong, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Organizing reports, (Dominic Chan), 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Organizing reports, (David Bacon), 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Organizing reports, (Augustin Ramirez), 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Organizing Department, 1985-1990 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Organizers training, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Local 213, Elections, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Local 214, Elections, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Local 215, Elections, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Local 101, Elections, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- STX, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Convention, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Department of Associate Membership, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Convention Resolutions, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Convention/GEB logistics, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Convention Meetings/Programs, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Convention, letter to members, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Convention, Committee on Labor Standards, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Convention, delegate credentials, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Staff meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Officers' meetings, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Niemand Statesville Strike, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Persian Gulf War, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Clippings, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Textile, Apparel, Footwear Trade Act of 1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Textile, Apparel, and Footwear Trade Act of 1990 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Labor legislation, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Misc. (loose in box) (Box 9, Folder 29)
  no date
- Katie Quan correspondence, June, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Katie Quan correspondence, May, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Katie Quan correspondence, April, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Katie Quan correspondence, March, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Katie Quan correspondence, March, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Katie Quan correspondence, February, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Katie Quan correspondence, January, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Katie Quan correspondence, May, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Katie Quan correspondence, December, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Katie Quan correspondence, November, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Katie Quan correspondence, October, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Katie Quan correspondence, September, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Katie Quan correspondence, September, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Katie Quan correspondence, August, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Katie Quan correspondence, August, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Katie Quan correspondence, July, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Katie Quan correspondence, June, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Katie Quan correspondence, June, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Katie Quan correspondence, April, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Katie Quan correspondence, March, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Katie Quan correspondence, February, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Katie Quan correspondence, January, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Katie Quan correspondence, January, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- ABC Sewing, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Kin Hing, signed authorizations, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Kin Hing, originals of forms, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Kin Hing, press coverage, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Kin Hing, backups/questionnaires, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Kin Hing, bankruptcy, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Kin Hing, copies of claims, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Kong, taxes, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Kong, Byer Reserve, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Kong, October follow-ups, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Kong, "hot goods', 1991 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Kong, Byer money, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Kong, NSF (non-sufficient funds) checks, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Kong, bankruptcy claims, wages, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Kong, bankruptcy claims, loans, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Kong, NSF checks, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Kong, loan claims, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Kong, loans, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Kong, Mercedes Benz, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Kong, Goodies, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Kong, jobs, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Kong, shop, delegate lists, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Kong, list of workers, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Kong, individual follow-ups, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Kong, individual follow-ups, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Kong, claims to Labor Commission, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Kong, exceptions, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- prepared fax forms for press releases, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- completed claims-to be copied, filed with commission, added to totals (includes lists), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Kong, press release, July 26, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Kong, press release, August 2, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Kong, press release, August 7, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Kong, press release, August 13, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Kong, press release, August 23, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Kong, press release, September 27, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Kong, clippings, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Kong, clippings, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Kong, clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Kong, press release, July 24, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Kong, authorizations without matching claims, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Kong, signed authorizations, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Kong, authorization forms, blank, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Kong, health insurance, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Kong, loans, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Kong, plumbing, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Kong, notes from meeting, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Kong, E.D.D. claim, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Kong, name list of workers, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Kong, bankruptcy payout, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Kong, bankruptcy news, 1991-1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Kong, bankruptcy news, 1991-1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Kong, special fund follow-up, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Kong, special fund distribution, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Kong, special fund consolidated, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Kong, special fund, press coverage, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Kong, Victoria Bradshaw, California Labor Commissioner, October 15, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Kong, special fund responses, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Kong, special fund case, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Kong, special fund politicking, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Kong, Mondale Chan, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Kong, Yee Nor, Criminal case, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Kong, Workers Committee, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Kong, Raymond Kong, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Kong, workers signed letters to mayor, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Kong, health, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Kong, legal notes, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Kong, wage claims, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Kong, special fund disbursement, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Kong, wage pay authorization, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Kong, tax, W-2, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Kong, federal bankruptcy, 1991-1996 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Kong, receivership, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Kong, machine auction, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Kong, knit machine fraud, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Kong, receiver's first interim report, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Kong, receiver's 2nd interim report, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Kong, receivers reports, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Kong, receivers reports, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Kong, loan recovery, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Kong, district attorney, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Kong, The Gap, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Kong, Calvin Klein, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Kong, manufacturer's liability, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Kong, hot goods injunction, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Kong, special fund, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Kong, special funds, politicians, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Kong, New Knitwear, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Kong, photos, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Kong, clippings, 1991-1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Koret, Chico incentive, 1989-1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Koret, Roger Bagley, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Koret, Chico walkout, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Koret, Chico walkout, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Koret, Cathy Wolf, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Koret, Chico walkout, proposed settlements, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Koret, Chico walkout arbitration proceedings, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Koret, Chico walkout, correspondence, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Koret, Chico walkout, Kathy Quan correspondence, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Koret, Chico walkout, Robert Bagley, Kathy Quan notes, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Koret, Chico walkout, duplicate copies, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Koret, Chico walkout, notes, December 6, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Koret, Seal #1, plant closure notes, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Koret, Seal 1, notice to workers, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Koret, Seal 1, notes and reference, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Koret, Seal 1, union position, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Koret, Seal 1, negotiation notes, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Koret, Seal 1, company position, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Koret, Seal 1, settlement drafts, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Koret, Seal 1, (#9,#10 Howard) Closure WARN, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Koret, Seal plant club, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Koret, Seal Private Industry Council, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Koret, Seal 1, Private Industry Council, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Koret, Workers Committee, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Koret Seal, Center for Working Life, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Koret, boycott, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Koret, Seal 1, politicians, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Koret, Seal 1, severance lists, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Koret, Seal 1, EE notice, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Koret, clippings, media, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Koret, finances, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Koret, corporate information, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Koret, contractors, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Koret, withdrawal liability, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Koret, Koret Foundation, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Koret, plant closures research, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Labor Research Group, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Koret Board of Supervisors Resolution, James Ho (SF Deputy Mayor), letter, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Lilli Ann, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Lilli Ann, clippings, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Movie star, settlement, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Movie star, organizing, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Movie star, Gap, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Movie star, corporate research, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Movie star, bankruptcy, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Movie star, clippings, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Movie star, Department of Labor, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Movie star/Ocean, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- press list, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Contracto Espanol, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- SF Knitworks Analysis de Precios, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- SF Knitworks, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- SFK, Calvin Klein and SFK, Jay Mazur, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- SFK, Cartas a Clientes, February 3, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- SFK, Cartas a Trabajadores, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- SFK, Christian Dior, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- SFK, Correspondencia Clientes, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- SFK, customers, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- SF Knitworks, customer, Adrienne Vittadini, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- SF Knitworks, customer, Anne Klein, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- SF Knitworks, customer, Aurea, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- SFK, customer, Ballinger Gold, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- SFK, customer, Banana Republic, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- SFK, customer, Calvin Klein, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- SFK, customer, Carole Little, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- SFK, customers, Colours, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- SFK, customer, Cousin Johnny, 1995-1998 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- SF Knitworks, customer, Bobby Jones, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- SFK, customer, DKNY, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- SFK, customer, Dana Buchanan/Liz Cair, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- SFK, customer, Eddie Bauer, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- SFK, customer, Ellen Tracy, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- SFK, customer, Gap, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- SFK, customer, Genie International, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- SFK, customer, Gymboree, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- SFK, customer, Hampshire Designers, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- SFK, customer, Hanna Anderson, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- SFK, customer, L.L. Bean, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- SFK, (customer, Lands End) Ed Tchakalian, Milwaukee, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- SFK, customer, Land's End, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- SFK, customer, Lilli Ann, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 47)